question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The octopus has three hearts.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Koalas are a type of bear.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Bats are blind.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The color red makes bulls aggresive.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Only female mosquitoes bite.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "An earthworm split in half becomes two worms",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Hummingbirds are the only birds that can fly backwards.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "giraffes have just as many bones in their neck as humans.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Fleas can jump 350 times its body length.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Polar bear skin is the same color as it's fur.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
